crispygamer.com 2009-06-16

# Crispy Gamer | Privacy Policy

Last updated January 1, 2008 

This Privacy Policy is applicable to all web sites (also, the "Website" or the "Service") operated by Crispy Gamer and domains owned by Crispy Gamer where this policy is displayed. This Privacy Policy is part of and is subject to our Terms of Use. All capitalized terms used but not defined herein shall have the meaning attributed thereto in the Terms of Use 

**Personally Identifiable Data Collected by Crispy Gamer**

We collect Personal Information when you voluntarily choose to provide such Personal Information, such as when you contact us with inquiries, respond to one of our surveys, register on the Website, or use our services. For instance, when you register on the Website, we may ask for certain information, such as your first and last name, gamer name, email address, or mobile number. (You can access and update certain of your information by accessing the "Update My Account" Web page. If you have difficulty reaching this page, please visit our "Customer Feedback" Web page.) 

**Other Information Collected**

**Non-Identifiable Information**

During or after registration, or in connection with other interactive features such as entering a contest or promotion, Crispy Gamer may also ask for other information which cannot presently be used to specifically identify you, such as your personal interests (including favorite activity and destination), birth date, occupation, postal code, year of birth, gender, and income range. This information will be lined with your Personal Information. Crispy Gamer might collect this information through personal interest forms, surveys, or contests. We also ask whether you want to receive emails from us or special offers from partners. See the section on "Sharing of Data" for further detail. 

**IP Addresses and Browser Information**

Our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard disk so that the website can remember who you are. A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the "lifetime" of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number. 

When you visit our website, we send you a cookie. Cookies may be used in the following ways: 

  * To help us recognize you as a unique visitor (just a number) when you return to our website, to allow us to tailor content or advertisements to match your preferred interests, or to avoid showing you the same advertisements repeatedly.
  * To develop leads for our internal sales group and our business partners and provide direct marketing communications to you if you have explicitly consented to receive such communications. 
  * Do not attempt to harvest or collect any personal information, including account names, from the Website, nor use any means of communication provided by the Website (forums, blogs, user comments, etc.) for any commercial solicitation purposes.
  * To compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our site and to help us improve the structure of our website. We cannot identify you personally in this way.

Two types of cookies may be used on this website: session cookies (which are temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the site) and persistent cookies (which remain in the cookie file of your browser for much longer, though how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie). 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser, as well as delete any cookies that have been installed in the cookie folder of your browser. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our site if cookies are disabled/deleted. If you do not know how to disable or delete cookies for the browser you are using, you should select 'cookies' in the Help function of your browser to get more information. 

**Aggregated Personal Data**

In an effort to better understand and serve the users of our services, we may conduct research on our user demographics, interests, and behavior based on Personal Information and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and Crispy Gamer may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents, and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. Crispy Gamer may also disclose aggregated use statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for lawful purposes. 

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California Law, California residents have the right to request in writing from businesses with whom they have an established business relationship, (1) a list of the categories of personal information, such as name, address, e-mail address, and the type of services provided to the customer, that a business has disclosed to third parties (including affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties' direct marketing purposes, and (2) the names and addresses of all such third parties. To request the above information, please write to us at: Privacy Coordinator, Crispy Gamer, 35 West 36th Street, Suite 4W, New York, NY 10018 with a reference to California Disclosure Information. 

We will respond to such written requests within 30 days following receipt at the mailing address stated above. If we receive your request at a different mailing address, we will respond within a reasonable period of time, but not to exceed 150 days from the date received. Please note that we are only required to respond to each customer once per calendar year. 

**Consent**

BY SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US, AND/OR BY USING OUR SITE, YOU AGREE THAT WE MAY COLLECT, USE AND DISCLOSE SUCH PERSONAL INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND AS PERMITTED OR REQUIRED BY LAW. 

If you do not agree with these terms, do not provide any Personal Information to us. If you refuse or withdraw your consent, or if you choose not to provide us with any required Personal Information, we may not be able to provide you with products or services that can be offered on our Website. 

**Children**

Crispy Gamer does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Information through the Website. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Information on this Website without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to Crispy Gamer through this Website, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases. 

**Public Forums & Reviews**

Crispy Gamer makes personalized profile pages and groups available to its members, as well as allowing you to submit reviews about your gaming experiences or about gaming products and services. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas may become public information, depending upon the preferences you select. Accordingly, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in such a forum. 

**Use Of Personal Information and Other Information**

Crispy Gamer uses the Personal Information you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Information for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Information in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by e-mail, we will use the Personal Information you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Information in order to obtain access to the Crispy Gamer services, we will use your Personal Information to provide you with access to such services and to monitor your use of such services. Crispy Gamer and its subsidiaries and affiliates may also use your Personal Information and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Website to help us improve the content and functionality of the Website, to better understand our users and to improve the Crispy Gamer Services. Crispy Gamer and its affiliates may use this information to contact you in the future to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "opt-out" of receiving future communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below. 

If Crispy Gamer intends on using any Personal Information in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Information is collected. 

**Disclosure Of Personal Information and Other Information**

Crispy Gamer shares your Personal Information with third parties only with your express permission, or as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy. Crispy Gamer is not in the business of selling your information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal information with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below. 

  * Select Partners and Affiliates: Crispy Gamer may share your Personal Information with a third party when, if in acting on a third party promotion described in an e-mail we have sent or on our Website, you provide additional Personal Information and you consent to that Personal Information being shared with the designated partner. Additionally, if a contest is sponsored by or together with any of Crispy Gamer's strategic partners, we may share information with that sponsor. By entering the contest you are consenting to our sponsor receiving the information you provide with your entry. That partner will have its own privacy policy that governs its use of the information you provide. 
  * To develop leads for our internal sales group and our business partners and provide direct marketing communications to you if you have explicitly consented to receive such communications.
  * Co-branded Websites that Offer Merchandise: Crispy Gamer may have links to the Web sites of other entities to allow you to purchase merchandise. These Web sites may look similar to Crispy Gamer, but are run by separate entities with whom Crispy Gamer has partnered (look in your browser bar to determine if you are still on an Crispy Gamer Web site, located at www.crispygamer.com). Crispy Gamer receives a commission for any purchases you make on partner sites. To help calculate these commissions, Crispy Gamer sends a tracking number to the partners. We do not provide Personal Information to our merchandise partners (except with your permission or as otherwise mentioned herein). Our merchandise partners provide us with aggregate purchase data, no individual purchase data is disclosed. Each partner site has its own privacy policy on gathering information from you. You may wish to check this policy before giving out Personal Information directly to any merchandise provider. Crispy Gamer does not control how a partner uses information gathered on its site.
  * Aggregated Data: Crispy Gamer will provide aggregate, anonymous information (e.g. "55% of our visitors enjoy <<___________>>") to advertisers and third parties. Such aggregate data cannot be linked to any one person.
  * Required Disclosure: Crispy Gamer will disclose Personal Information when it believes it is required to do so by law enforcement or other appropriate governmental authorities, or if the Personal Information is pertinent in a legal proceeding or court action.
  *   * Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy Web sites or other assets. In such transactions, Personal Information may be one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that third parties or Crispy Gamer merges with or sells all or substantially all of its assets to another company, Personal Information collected on Crispy Gamer web sites may be one of the transferred assets.
  * 

**Advertising Services**

Third parties advertise on our Website, and we also contract with third parties to serve ads across the Internet. These third parties may serve ads about our products or services, or third party products or services in which, based on your Session Data, we or our business partners believe you may be interested. 

While we may share Session Data (as defined above) with third parties to help facilitate the serving of these ads, we do not share any Personal Information about you unless you give us permission to do so (which permission may be granted by declining to opt-out,) separate from any permission you provide when you register on the Website. These third parties may seek to use cookies and pixel tags, including those collected on our Website, to track Session Data about the ads you have seen and types of things in which you appear interested. These third parties may also use combined information about your visits to our Website and other sites in order to provide advertisements about related goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

When you click on a third party advertisers' link from our Website, you will be taken off of our Website and will enter the third party's site. We are not responsible for such third party's sites. You should carefully review the privacy statements of any other site you visit, because those privacy statements will apply to your visit to that site, and may be very different from our Privacy Policy. 

**Email**

From time to time we may provide special offers on this Website, or may send special email offers about our products and services. Or, if you elected to receive them, (which permission may be granted by declining to opt-out) those of selected partners or our affiliated companies. Crispy Gamer will not send you any email that you do not wish to receive. If you wish to receive newsletters and special offers by email from Crispy Gamer, selected partners, or our affiliated companies, you can visit the "Edit Profile" Web page. If at any time you wish to unsubscribe from any of Crispy Gamer's email products, either click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of these communications or visit the "Edit Profile" Web page and deselect the email products that you no longer wish to receive. Please allow up to 15 days for changes to your subscription status to be made. To access this Web page, you will need to be logged-in to Crispy Gamer, which may require you to type-in your id and password. If you are having difficulty reaching our Edit Profile page, please access The Contact Us page by clicking the link found at the bottom of every page.

**Crispy Gamer's "Customer Feedback" Web page.**

Periodically, Crispy Gamer introduces new email products or improves existing ones. If you are subscribed to an Crispy Gamer email product we may provide you with a trial subscription to the new product. You may unsubscribe from any of these products at any time. 

We use an email system that can individually track who opens an email (if you receive the email in HTML format) and who clicks on any link contained in an email. This is Personal Information, which we collect to: 

  * calculate how many people were interested in particular topics or particular links contained in an email product; and 
  * provide personalized services that are best suited to your interests

If you do not wish such information to be collected about you, you should unsubscribe from our emails. 

**Security**

Crispy Gamer employs physical, administrative and technical safeguards to help protect the confidentiality and integrity of Personal Information and to reduce the risk of loss, misuse, unauthorized access disclosure or modification of Personal Information. 

As a further security precaution, Crispy Gamer asks you to provide a password when you register on our Websites. You then have the option of storing that password on a cookie set on your computer. This way, you need not type in the password when you again access one of our sites. 

If the computer you are using is not for your sole use, after you have finished accessing an Crispy Gamer Web site, you should click on the this link, which will sign you off of the Web site. This action prevents other people from accessing your information. When you want to access member-only areas of Crispy Gamer's Web sites at another time, you will need to sign-in and type-in your password. You will have the option of having your password e-mailed to you if you have forgotten what it is. 

If you choose to contact the Crispy Gamer through our Website, you should be aware that any information transmitted electronically via the World Wide Web might not be secure. Crispy Gamer assumes no liability for the loss of any information that you transmit to us via the World Wide Web. 

In communicating with you, we may send e-mail as unencrypted plain text because we are aware that many users cannot readily process encrypted e-mail. This is done for your convenience, but with the security concern that, if misrouted or intercepted, it could be read more easily than encrypted e-mail. We may also communicate with you via mobile phone. We cannot guarantee the privacy or security of any communications transmitted via mobile phone. 

**Changes in Privacy Policy**

As the nature of our business changes, Crispy Gamer may need to change its Privacy Policy. If this Privacy Policy is changed, this page will be updated. If there is a material change to this policy we will notify all users who are currently receiving email from Crispy Gamer. 

If you have any questions or suggestions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us. Alternatively, you can mail Crispy Gamer at: 

Privacy Coordinator  
Crispy Gamer, Inc.  
35 West 36th Street, Suite 4W  
New York, NY. 10018 

Only questions about Crispy Gamer's Privacy Policy should be addressed to the above addresses. Any inquiries sent to these addresses that are not related to the Privacy Policy will not be reviewed. You may address other concerns regarding Crispy Gamer, by visiting the "Customer Feedback" Web page.
